wholelattelove.com 2011-11-26

# 

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers wholelattelove.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the wholelattelove.com site. 

**Information Collection & Use**  
Whole Latte Love collects personally identifiable information when you register for an account and when you use certain products or services. When you register with Whole Latte Love, we will ask for your name, address ande-mail address. Whole Latte Love uses this information for two general purposes: To fulfill your requests for certain products and services and to customize the advertising and content you see through the following methods:

  * **Newsletter**  
Please note: When you sign up for an account or place an order with Whole Latte Love, your email address is automatically entered into our newsletter database. The newsletter is generally sent out once a month, it offers coupon codes, sale items, feature products, and informative articles. Simply click on the unsubscribe button, found at the bottom of the newsletter, if you do not wish receive future newsletters. Email addresses are not sold or shared with other companies. They are used solely by Whole Latte Love. 
  * **Email-Exclusive Offers  
** Due to ever changing spam and privacy filters, please be aware that **email communications,** sent from **WholeLatteLove,** may end up in your **junk mail or spam mail** folders. So, when you are expecting e-mail from us, don't forget to check these folders. To ensure you receive our exclusive offers, add our email address to your address book. Email addresses are not sold or shared with other companies. They are used solely by Whole Latte Love.

**Information Sharing & Disclosure**  
Whole Latte Love will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information. Whole Latte Love will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people only when: (1) We have your consent to share the information. (2) We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested. (3) We need to send the information to companies who work on our behalf to provide a product or service to you. Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us. (4) We're required to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.

**Changes to Policy Page**  
Whole Latte Love may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

**Questions & Suggestions**  
If you have questions or suggestions, please send an e-mail to [sales@wholelattelove.com](mailto:sales@wholelattelove.com).

Top Of Page

## Security Policy

Ensuring the security and protection of your personal information is important to us. When you choose to purchase from Whole Latte Love, you will be taken to a secure web page to enter credit card information to complete the purchase. 

Whole Latte Love only uses 128-bit SSL encryption. SSL technology encodes information as it is being sent over the Internet, helping to ensure that the information transmitted remains confidential. 

SSL technology requires the use of compatible browsers, which allow you to communicate with our website in a protected session by encrypting information that flows between you and the site. Internet Explorer browser versions prior to 3.02 and Netscape browser versions prior to 4.02 are not capable of 128-bit encryption. We recommend you use the latest browser versions available.
